there are three ways to send either from
有三种方法可以将合同中的任何一个发送到另一个合同
contract to another contract the three
methods are transferred sand and coal
的方法是转移沙和煤，并建议在2019年后采用的方法
and the recommended way after 2019
December is to use coal so in this video
12月将使用煤炭，因此在此视频中，我们将介绍一些细微之处
we're going to go over the subtle
differences between the three methods
三种方法之间的差异，并查看为什么调用是推荐的方法
and see why call is the recommended way
to send either
在合同使用转移方式时发送
when a contract uses the transfer method
to send either it forwards 2300 gas on
在收到合同时向另一方发送2300天然气
the other side when a contract receives
an either by any of these three methods
这三种方法中的任何一种都有一个特殊的功能
there is a special function that gets
called and that function is called the
被调用，该函数被称为后备函数，并且自转移以来
fallback function and since the transfer
function for 2,800 gas this means that
2800种气体的功能，这意味着后备功能最多具有2200种气体
the fallback function has at most 2200
gas to spend and if the transfer fails
花费的汽油，以及由于某种原因（例如，用完了）而导致转移失败的情况
for some reason such as running out of
gas trying to send more ether than the
试图发送比合约电话更多的以太币或试图发送给
contract calls or trying to send to a
non payable address then the function
非应付款地址，然后功能为千人，交易失败
thousand-aire and the transaction fails
let the transfer function above the
让函数上方的传递函数将其2300气体发送到
function send for its 2300 gas to the
contract receiving the heater
接收加热器的合同与转移不同，它返回布尔值
unlike transfer it returns a boolean
value when the send function is
发送函数成功时返回的值，否则返回true
successful it returns true otherwise it
returns false using the call function
使用调用函数返回false，您可以负担所有费用或
you can it afford all of the gas or
specify the amount of gas that you're
指定您要转发的气体量，例如发送的气体量
going to forward and like the send
function it returns a boolean value and
函数将返回布尔值，并且在2019年12月之后，这是
after December of 2019 this is the
recommended method to use the reason is
推荐使用的方法的原因是，将来天然气的成本可以
that in the future the cost of gas can
change for different operations at the
这两个功能转移时，针对不同的操作而改变
moment these two functions transference
and guard against the reaction see hack
并防止反应，仅转发2300汽油即可看到骇客，您
by forwarding only 2300 gas and you
can't do much with 2300 gas so if a
2300汽油不能做太多事情，所以如果收到以太币的合约回电了
contract receiving the ether calls back
into the contract that CELTA ether then
进入CELTA醚的合同中，那么它只需要消耗2,300瓦斯，现在让我们
it only has 2,300 gas to spend now let's
imagine a case where in the future the
想象一个情况，将来某个操作的天然气成本为
cost of gas for some operation is
and now all of a sudden 2,300 gas might
现在突然有2300种汽油可能足以造成一些破坏
be enough to do some damage
so in summary from now on use call to
因此，从现在开始，总而言之，请致电将其发送给另一个合同并保卫
send it to another contract and guard
against the engine see by making all
在调用另一个之前，先进行所有状态更改，然后再对引擎进行查看
state changes before you call another
contract and also by using modifiers
以及使用防止引擎发动的修饰语，请参见
that guard against to the engine see in
a future video we'll go over the
未来的视频中，我们将进行反应，请参阅hack和更多详细信息，因此
reaction see hack and more details so
stay tuned now that we went over the
请继续关注，我们已经详细了解了团队努力的技术细节，
technical details of the team efforts to
send eater to another contract let's
将食客发送到另一个合同让我们编写一些实际代码以将食客发送到
write some actual code to send eater to
another contract first we're gonna
首先要签订另一个合同，我们将要创建一个合同
create a contract that is going to
receive the eater and in order for this
接收食者，并且为了使该合同能够通过三者接收以太币
contract to receive ether via the three
methods mentioned above we need to
上面提到的方法，我们需要声明一个称为后备功能的函数
declare a function called a fallback
function and you declare it like this
函数，并且您像这样声明它，该函数不能为其命名
this function cannot have a name it
cannot take any inputs and it cannot
不能接受任何输入，也不能返回任何输出
return any outputs furthermore the
visibility of the fallback function must
后备功能的可见性必须在外部，并且为了
be external and in order for the
fallback function to receive either it
后备功能以接收它必须被声明为应付款，我们也是
has to be declared as payable we're also
going to create a helper function so
要创建一个辅助函数，以便我们可以检查以太币的余额
that we could check the balance of ether
in this contract and I explained how
在这份合同中，我在上一个视频中解释了此功能的工作原理
this function works in a previous video
about payable in short all address type
简而言之，所有地址类型都有一个称为余额的特殊属性
has a special property called balance
which stores the amount of ether that
它存储了该地址持有的以太币数量，在这里我们要说的是
the address holds and here we're saying
get the balance of ether stored in this
获取此合同中存储的以太币余额，从而完成合同
contract so this completes the contract
that will receive the ether and now
将会接收到以太币，现在继续前进，我们来写合约
moving on let's write the contract that
will send the heater
将向加热器发送我要说明的第一种方法
the first method that I'm gonna explain
is the transfer method so I'm gonna name
是转移方法，所以我将这个函数命名为转移发送，我们
this function send by transfer and we're
gonna pass the address that we're gonna
要传递我们要发送给食客的地址，现在为了回想起
send eater to now recall that in order
for this address to be able to receive
为了使该地址能够接收以太币，必须声明该地址
an ether this address has to be declared
as payable so we're gonna do that right
应付帐款，所以我们现在要去做，我要命名这个地址
now and I'm gonna name this address
input as to this function will be public
关于此功能的输入将是公开的，并且也将是有偿的，因为
and it's also going to be payable since
we're gonna send Ito from our account to
我们将从帐户中将伊藤发送到此合同
this contract
and forward the ether to the receive
并把以太转发给上面的接收者合同，然后将其发送出去
eater contract above and to send it over
transfer you call the transfer method on
转移您可以在括号内的地址上调用转移方法
the address inside the parentheses we
put in the amount of ether that we're
放入我们将要转移的乙醚量，我们将全部转移
gonna transfer we're gonna forward all
of the ether that we send from our
从我们的帐户发送的以太币中，我们可以通过放置
account and we can do that by putting
message top value here which holds that
消息的最高值，此处包含随此发送的以太币数量
amount of ether that was sent with this
transaction and in this case it will be
交易，在这种情况下，这将是我们将成为食客的数量
the amount of eater that we'll be
sending from our account so this is how
从我们的帐户发送，这样您就可以使用以下方式将食客发送到另一个地址
you send eater to another address using
the transfer method now the transfer
现在的传输方式传输方式会将2300瓦斯输送到
method will forward 2300 gas to this
address and if for some reason this
地址，如果由于某种原因该功能未能发送进餐者，则此
function fails to send eater then this
method will turn error and the
方法将转为错误，并且交易将失败，因此，如果您尝试
transaction will fail so if you try to
send eternal contract that does not have
发送没有应付款回退功能的永恒合同，则此
a payable fallback function then this
transfer method will fail and the
转移方法将失败，并且事务也将失败
transaction will also fail another
possible reason that this method can
该方法失败的可能原因是当您尝试发送更多食者时
fail is when you try to send more eater
than the contract holes so for example
而不是合同孔，例如，如果合同孔了一个食者，而您
if the contract holes one eater and you
try to send 10 meters then this function
尝试发送10米，然后此功能将失败接下来让我们谈谈发送
will fail next let's talk about the send
method we're gonna create another
方法，我们将创建另一个函数，并且函数签名将
function and the function signature will
be mostly the same as sent by transfer
基本上与转帐发送的相同，我们称此功能为转寄
and we'll call this function send by
send and the syntax to send either using
send和使用send方法发送的语法类似于
the send method is similar to the
transfer method I like to transfer a
转移方法我喜欢转移如果失败会引发错误的方法
method that throws an error if it fails
to send either the send method returns a
发送方法send方法返回一个布尔值，该布尔值指示是否
boolean value that indicates whether it
was able to send the heater or not so
是否能够发送加热器，所以在这里我们将捕获结果
here we're gonna capture the result in a
boolean variable called sent and since
布尔值变量send，因为我们希望事务在失败的情况下失败
we want the transaction to fail if it
fails to send eater here we're going to
无法在此处发送食者，我们将要求发送的布尔值是
require that the boolean value sent is
equal to true if it is false then the
如果它为假，则等于true，那么require将变成错误，并且
require will turn error and the
transaction will fail so that's how you
事务将失败，因此这就是您使用send方法和
send either using the send method and
finally let's talk about how to send
最后，让我们讨论一下如何使用call方法将名称发送
either using the call method will name
the function sent by call other than
通过调用发送的函数，除了函数签名相同
that the function signature is the same
as the two functions above to send
作为上述两个功能，您可以使用调用方法进行发送
either using the call method you do it
like this now this looks complex and it
像现在这样看起来很复杂，看起来好像在做很多事情
looks like it's doing a lot of things
here but I'll go over call in more
在这里，但我将在另一个视频中详细讨论您需要的内容
details in another video what you need
to know here is that this function will
要知道的是，此功能将转发您发送的所有来宾
forward all of the guests that you sent
to the address that is receiving data
到接收数据的地址，以及是否要指定多少汽油
and if you want to specify how much gas
that is being forwarded
正在转发，您现在可以这样做
you can do it like this now this
function will return two values the
函数将返回两个值，第一个输出是一个布尔值
first output is a boolean value that
indicates whether it was successful as
指示发送食者是否成功
sending eater or not the second part of
the up holds the return values from
向上保存调用后备函数的返回值
calling the fallback function
now since the fallback function cannot
现在，由于后备功能无法在这种情况下返回任何值，因此
return any values in this case this will
be an empty value in other words zero
为空值，换句话说为零字节，类似于send方法
bytes and similar to the send method
above here we're going to require that
在上面，我们将要求通过呼叫发送成功
sending either by call was successful
and now let's deploy the contracts and
现在让我们部署合同并测试功能
test the functions out
so here I've deployed the receive eater
所以在这里，我已经部署了“吃食者”合同和“食蚁兽”合同，
contract and thus anteater contract and
we're going to be sending either to this
我们将从该合同中发送该合同中的任何一个，让我们先
contract from this contract let's first
try the send by transfer function so I'm
尝试通过传送发送功能，以便将wecb的地址复制到
gonna copy the address of wecb to
contract and paste it in here and we'll
合同并粘贴在这里，我们将在这里发送一些仪表，我将发送一个
send some meters here I'm gonna send one
eater so I called this function and send
食者，所以我调用了此功能，并向该合同发送了一个电表，因此
one meter to this contract so the
balance of this contract should now be
该合同的余额现在应为一米，以便查看
one meter so to review what just
happened
当我们称其为我的传递函数时发生了
when we call this my transfer function
this code here was executed and they
此代码已在此处执行，它们在内部调用了fallback函数
call the fallback function inside the
receive eater contract and since the
收到食人合同，并且由于将后备功能声明为应付款
fallback function is declared as payable
it was able to receive the one eater
它能够接收我们发送的一个食者和所有这两个功能
that we sent and all the two functions
work in a similar way here by sent one
在此以类似的方式工作，即通过发送发送的一个涡轮和通过呼叫发送的一个涡轮
turbine sent by send and by sent by call
and as expected the balance is now 30
和预期的一样，现在的余额是30个以太币
ethers
so that covers the three ways to send
这样就涵盖了从合同发送的三种方式和三种
either from a contract and the three
ways to send dieter are transfer sand
送节食者的方法是转移沙子，并称转移性和福特的
and call both transference and Ford's
2300 gas to the contract that is
如果接收数据传输的2300天然气合同拖欠了空气
receiving data transfer tows an air if
it fails to send the ether and the send
它无法发送以太币，并且send方法返回布尔值，因此使用
method returns a boolean value so using
this method you will have to manually
这种方法，您将必须手动检查以太已发送呼叫是
check that the ether was sent call is a
low-level function that by default
默认情况下转发所有气体的低级功能，例如
forwards all of the gas and like the
send method it returns a boolean value
send方法返回一个布尔值，您必须手动检查
and you will have to manually check that
the ether was sent and the recommended
已发送以太币，推荐的方法是在2019年12月之前使用
method to use as of December of 2019 is
to use the call method using the call
要使用call方法来使用call方法，您必须编写防御性
method you'll have to write defensive
code that will guard against three
现在将在未来的视频中防止三引擎CX的代码
engine CX now in future videos we'll
dive deeper into the topics of fallback
深入探讨后备函数调用方法和可重入的主题
functions call method and the reentrant
z hack so stay tuned but for now that's
z hack，敬请关注，但就目前而言，这就是我发送加热器的全部内容
all I got to say about sending heater
thanks for watching and I'll see you in
感谢您的收看，我将在下一个视频中与您见面
the next video